<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-06-21T23:48:08-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Your awesome title</title><subtitle>Write an awesome description for your new site here. You can edit this line in _config.yml. It will appear in your document head meta (for Google search results) and in your feed.xml site description.</subtitle><entry><title type="html">The Wooden Throne</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/21/the-wooden-throne.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Wooden Throne" /><published>2019-06-21T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-21T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/21/the-wooden-throne</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/21/the-wooden-throne.html">&lt;p&gt;A king born to claim the golden crown, wielding great power able to reshape entire continent. His soldiers were treated as sons in this cruel war and they followed him to the ends of the earth to slay fowl beasts and barbarians to claim glory for the kingdom. His forces were armed with strange magics, firing bolts of fire at their enemies. The enemy forces were mere insects under his boots,a short lived annoyance in his conquest for world dominion.He would instill strict laws upon his people and wiped out anyone who did not fit into the system he designed.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The empire soon stretched its borders across the world destroying vast cultures and ideologies that happened to be in his path. Even the gods sat on their celestial thrones in awe of his magnificent power knowing that one day he would challenge even the heavens.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;They called them immortals for they seemed to never die in battle nor bleed when struck by a blade. Their cold eyes peered at enemies with disgust, taking pleasure in curing the world of their species. This was the kings grand design, a perfect army to herald the perfect world. The war would in fact be prolonged to maintain this order, for as long as the people had something to fight there would be no disorder.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A king born to claim the golden crown, wielding great power able to reshape entire continent. His soldiers were treated as sons in this cruel war and they followed him to the ends of the earth to slay fowl beasts and barbarians to claim glory for the kingdom. His forces were armed with strange magics, firing bolts of fire at their enemies. The enemy forces were mere insects under his boots,a short lived annoyance in his conquest for world dominion.He would instill strict laws upon his people and wiped out anyone who did not fit into the system he designed.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Virtual Drug</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/20/virtual-drug.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Virtual Drug" /><published>2019-06-20T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-20T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/20/virtual-drug</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/20/virtual-drug.html">&lt;p&gt;The mind often drifts to a certain abyss when confronted by the terrors of boredom. The joys once lived by times past are eclipsed by the present moment and they soon begin to resemble an endless prison without an escape. Anxiety fills the soul and sweat starts to bubble, the signs of an addiction is the sign of a struggle. The virtual world is often a lot less disappointing than reality. The vivid control you have over your virtual self contrast the chaos that torments everyday reality. From saving the universe from being devoured by fluffy rabbits, to punching trees under the cold purple skies, the realm of video games provide emotions that many be lacking in everyday life&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tendrils begin to sprout and dig their way into our minds, soon an innocent joy evolves into an addiction based on lies. The best years of life pass by and you’ve achieved plenty of riches in virtual reality, but in a dark dungeon free from hope your body waste away in reality. Time no longer holds meaning as the months pass by like days and before you have a chance to react the ones you care about disappear in a haze.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The mind often drifts to a certain abyss when confronted by the terrors of boredom. The joys once lived by times past are eclipsed by the present moment and they soon begin to resemble an endless prison without an escape. Anxiety fills the soul and sweat starts to bubble, the signs of an addiction is the sign of a struggle. The virtual world is often a lot less disappointing than reality. The vivid control you have over your virtual self contrast the chaos that torments everyday reality. From saving the universe from being devoured by fluffy rabbits, to punching trees under the cold purple skies, the realm of video games provide emotions that many be lacking in everyday life</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Prison</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/19/the-prison.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Prison" /><published>2019-06-19T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-19T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/19/the-prison</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/19/the-prison.html">&lt;p&gt;Time slips past our fingers so easily as the years we cherish go by in a matter of days. That’s the thing with time it seems, as it stops for nobody these days. Not for the king of the world or the peasant in the slums and it seems that regardless of how much time we have it’s never enough. We scream at the top of our lungs cursing at the gods of death that preyed on us before our time, instead getting grim looks of disappointment for our useless lives. A soul without meaning or direction filled with self loathe and spreading its hate among others is only worthy to be placed in the realms of the condemned. Souls such as these normally die twice but not before infecting the world with their spite.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Listening to words of motivation certainly helps, but only for a minute is this feeling of bliss kept. At the beginning of every project we feel a crawling sensation, a horrifying enemy called resistance and temptation. This resistance drives us mad and can be lethal as it traps you in a prison so secure it knows no equal. Before you realise it your entire life has gone by and you wonder what the universe might have given you if you were just to ask. This prison for so many years instilled fear and regret and now you find yourself chained to a death bed. The sad truth is that this cycle will continue even after your death as your sons and daughters take your spot after you are long forgotten.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Time slips past our fingers so easily as the years we cherish go by in a matter of days. That’s the thing with time it seems, as it stops for nobody these days. Not for the king of the world or the peasant in the slums and it seems that regardless of how much time we have it’s never enough. We scream at the top of our lungs cursing at the gods of death that preyed on us before our time, instead getting grim looks of disappointment for our useless lives. A soul without meaning or direction filled with self loathe and spreading its hate among others is only worthy to be placed in the realms of the condemned. Souls such as these normally die twice but not before infecting the world with their spite.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Trapped In A Tin Can</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/18/trapped-in-a-tin-can.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Trapped In A Tin Can" /><published>2019-06-18T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-18T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/18/trapped-in-a-tin-can</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/18/trapped-in-a-tin-can.html">&lt;p&gt;It takes a brave soul to leave behind their family to venture into the unknowns and dance with the outer realms of death. Hundreds of young boots slush through the swamps, the song of gunfire fills the morning air. To die for one’s country is the greatest honor pushing these soldiers to perish without fear. Metal birds peck at each other in the air while the hungry war machines scan for enemies leaving no one spared. Each encounter carved deep in their minds just in case they were to survive. Even asleep they take aim for each other’s dreams, every opportunity is a chance to end the war.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The homeland media soon begin to spread their propaganda, stirring fear and anger in the hearts of the people. They paint great soldiers waving a flag to hide behind, romanticizing a war that no one stands behind. The kings put faith in our hearts with their speeches too, reassuring us that our cause is true. While our troops throw away their lives in battle our leaders enjoy a sip from their bottles because in the cold war there are no winners.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This war so long fought soon transforms into a playground of doubt. Comrades lost in battle scream, they will continue to live on in our thoughts. Slowly our lands are filled with mountains of lifeless souls indistinguishable from friend or foe. When fighting halts we soon forget why it even started, making accusations of where the first shots departed. Meanwhile, the profiteers of war sit and count their money feeding off our pain like a bear devouring honey.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The soldiers who come home are often broken and sometimes see an ungrateful country. The flashes of war keep them up at night and even after the battle is over they still continue to fight.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It takes a brave soul to leave behind their family to venture into the unknowns and dance with the outer realms of death. Hundreds of young boots slush through the swamps, the song of gunfire fills the morning air. To die for one’s country is the greatest honor pushing these soldiers to perish without fear. Metal birds peck at each other in the air while the hungry war machines scan for enemies leaving no one spared. Each encounter carved deep in their minds just in case they were to survive. Even asleep they take aim for each other’s dreams, every opportunity is a chance to end the war.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Cycle Of Kings</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/17/cycle-of-kings.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Cycle Of Kings" /><published>2019-06-17T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-17T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/17/cycle-of-kings</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/17/cycle-of-kings.html">&lt;p&gt;A rebel is born with fresh eyes and new beliefs, eager to take hold of their destiny. A revolutionary wanting freedom from the tyrants that rule the motherland, willing to do anything to set their country free. For centuries these royal bloodlines ruled our faith, controlling us with laws that culled the creativity from our minds. The kings we elected cared not for our health but instead for the mountains of their distasteful wealth. Watching our brothers die on meaningless battlefields turned this so-called empire into a breeding ground for rebellion.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Freedom doesn’t come free and the king never plays fair, his armies eclipse the rebellion and he rules his people with fear. The hearts of the masses are sometimes hard to sway but despite this the rebellion grows every day. Strong leaders and motivators soon rise from the forge of oppression encouraging the people to stand against their depression. Soon unlikely allies reveal themselves and coordinated strikes ensue. The king is slain and the capital claimed now we can finally have a prosperous nation. Now the participants would share their prize but gold tends to twist the mind and even brothers would kill each other to have the power to rule another. The once righteous rebellion became corrupt by the blood of greed leaving the last man standing declared the new king.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now the empire is free from the hands of a truly mad king, the animals that once ruled so mighty have fallen in the dirt, squirming like worms. As the empire accepts its new king, deep in the crowd of cheering peasants a child stands grim. His father died by the hands of the new king and his hateful heart instills rage within him. The cycle of kings again renews, bestowing the throne to someone much worse. Deep in the hearts of many rebels there is a lust to be like the cruel king, a cold leader who seems to have everything.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">A rebel is born with fresh eyes and new beliefs, eager to take hold of their destiny. A revolutionary wanting freedom from the tyrants that rule the motherland, willing to do anything to set their country free. For centuries these royal bloodlines ruled our faith, controlling us with laws that culled the creativity from our minds. The kings we elected cared not for our health but instead for the mountains of their distasteful wealth. Watching our brothers die on meaningless battlefields turned this so-called empire into a breeding ground for rebellion.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Floating Dreams</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/16/floating-dreams.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Floating Dreams" /><published>2019-06-16T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-16T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/16/floating-dreams</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/16/floating-dreams.html">&lt;p&gt;The alarm clock screamed for me to wake from my short slumber, its voice piercing the walls of my inner thought. It was the same cycle every day going to a job that filled my soul with loathe and rage, torturing every atom of my being as each second ticked away. It felt like I was chained to this idea of a honey pot that stood at the end of the rainbow when in fact I could lose this so-called steady job and end up in hell.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The world felt cold; I was a part of a machine that gave me enough to keep the gears turning but never once stopped to ask my name. It was all for the money that’s how they catch the majority, paying enough to fuel our obsession with vanity. I was trapped like a rat in a golden prison selling my soul to impress my cellmates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At the edge of a cliff and the end of my rope I was given a choice, either keep my job and drift slowly into the realms of insanity or starve to death creating something that I truly enjoyed. Either way, the chance of failure was equal at both ends but at least doing what I loved would allow the ship to sink on my terms. As I lay here on this wooden bench, gazing at the stars, I pray to the gods I made the right choice.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The alarm clock screamed for me to wake from my short slumber, its voice piercing the walls of my inner thought. It was the same cycle every day going to a job that filled my soul with loathe and rage, torturing every atom of my being as each second ticked away. It felt like I was chained to this idea of a honey pot that stood at the end of the rainbow when in fact I could lose this so-called steady job and end up in hell.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Machine Empire</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/15/the-machine-empire.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Machine Empire" /><published>2019-06-15T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-15T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/15/the-machine-empire</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/15/the-machine-empire.html">&lt;p&gt;The day the machines were invented seemed like a lifetime ago, it went by almost in an instant. Efficient calculations made them useful for the sciences while their flashing pixels kept us entertained for generations. We used this modern day magic to establish a consciousness that radiated the entire globe giving every human the ability to coexist in a digital world. We even built screens to these new lands, a gateway to a realm that consumed our attention beyond control. They harvest our thoughts with each click, knowing what we want before we even think. Welcome to the modern era where artificial intelligence has already taken over and humanity is too dumb to realize it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are at a point in history where artificial intelligence is still relatively young and our future could go in any direction. Either we nuke each other into oblivion or build machines to do it for us. Most likely when this technology matures enough governments will start using it for militaristic purposes, producing weapons and fueling almost infinite machine armies built in a battery of well-streamlined factories all controlled by one hyper-intelligent AI. We often give enemies the tools necessary to stage our defeat and based on history along with or love for automation this is the most likely direction. Its the biggest fear that surrounds artificial intelligence, to have them forcefully wipe out our entire existence without a second thought. We may win a war against them and even learn something along the way or maybe die at the hands of our creation extinguished at our peak. Whatever the outcome I believe hyper-intelligent AI will completely flip this world on its head and I for one would welcome our new robotic overlords.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A more optimistic future would include machines doing all the heavy lifting for us in terms of taking over repetitive jobs to give humans more time to focus on science and culture. Instead of doing things we hate and leading miserable lives, we would enjoy our short existence in this universe. Advances may even allow us to fully merge with them and become superhuman leaving behind these weak mortal shells for a more metallic frame. Our carefree culture might lead us into a state where we heavily depend on robots to survive and not able to complete even the most menial of tasks. In the end, artificial intelligence, although risky, is our only shot at ascending beyond mortality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">The day the machines were invented seemed like a lifetime ago, it went by almost in an instant. Efficient calculations made them useful for the sciences while their flashing pixels kept us entertained for generations. We used this modern day magic to establish a consciousness that radiated the entire globe giving every human the ability to coexist in a digital world. We even built screens to these new lands, a gateway to a realm that consumed our attention beyond control. They harvest our thoughts with each click, knowing what we want before we even think. Welcome to the modern era where artificial intelligence has already taken over and humanity is too dumb to realize it.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Stairway To Infinity</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/14/stairway-to-infinity.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Stairway To Infinity" /><published>2019-06-14T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-14T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/14/stairway-to-infinity</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/14/stairway-to-infinity.html">&lt;p&gt;Pitch black darkness. I would imagine this was our life before birth, suspended in nothingness and truly at peace. Our modern lives contrast these early beginnings however as even the world we call home was forged in a fiery nest nurtured by chaos. Most of us are born to struggle in the mud lands of our own problems and not many find their escape. Countless get devoured by their demons and those who survive either come out the other side broken or rise to become immortals. This eternal fight is what fueled our species to adapt and achieve greatness beyond comprehension. It’s a lifetime of mistakes that have contributed to the success of humanity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The journey is long and we often find ourselves lost in the cruel sea of thought, crafting problems in our head before they have the chance to attack. The overwhelming burdens of life force us to look back at the simpler times when the world seemed open and new. We find innocent babies so adorable as they fumble about trying to exist, I wonder if the gods look down upon us thinking the same thing as we try to understand the complex threads that make up the fabric of reality.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In the end, we all have potential, like a blank canvas we can all grow into a masterpiece. We humans possess a tool that can mold this world into anything. Never in the history of mankind have we had the power to access knowledge so freely and almost instantaneously. The ability to be everywhere and having a voice that echos the globe would be considered magic a few centuries ago. It makes you wonder what this world will look like in the next hundred years. Will it be a paradise or a technological nightmare? Whatever the outcome lets enjoy this blue rock together.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">Pitch black darkness. I would imagine this was our life before birth, suspended in nothingness and truly at peace. Our modern lives contrast these early beginnings however as even the world we call home was forged in a fiery nest nurtured by chaos. Most of us are born to struggle in the mud lands of our own problems and not many find their escape. Countless get devoured by their demons and those who survive either come out the other side broken or rise to become immortals. This eternal fight is what fueled our species to adapt and achieve greatness beyond comprehension. It’s a lifetime of mistakes that have contributed to the success of humanity.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">The Civilized Chimp</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/13/the-civilized-chimp.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="The Civilized Chimp" /><published>2019-06-13T00:00:00-12:00</published><updated>2019-06-13T00:00:00-12:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2019/06/13/the-civilized-chimp</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2019/06/13/the-civilized-chimp.html">&lt;p&gt;It all started with a spark that gave birth to humanity, the moment the universe would begin to bend to our will. We were just simple creatures with sharp sticks and a want for more. As a result we formed small groups and although weak alone, we stood strong in numbers. We elected wise kings to lead our newly born nations and crafted flags adorned with the symbols of our ideologies and organizations. We forged sharp sticks that evolved into deadly blades to slay our enemies to gain fame and with each continent conquered it added to the melting pot which was our culture. Monuments stood long after our civilization’s vanish as a reminder of a golden era that crumbled to the dusts of time. Nations are born out of the ashes of these fallen nations heralding the rise of a more modern era.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blades and cavalry soon transformed into guns and armored vehicles, war machines that screamed and whistled across the battlefield. It was a race to see who had the biggest stick and before we knew it we had the power to destroy each other with the push of a button. The global fear of nuclear death raining down on our heads rendered the classic eras of war unprofitable and dead thus spawning an age of peace and prosperity.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s a never ending tug of war between us and our curiosity for the unknown. The weapons we once used to destroy one another now allow us to reach beyond the glassy skies and into the event horizon. With each generation’s pass we built upon each other mistakes forming new ideas and theories about our ever expanding universe. With our rapid growth in the recent years coupled with our short temper its amazing that we haven’t completely annihilated each other. Touching the cosmos we’re right back where we started, just a curious ape with a lust for more power.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">It all started with a spark that gave birth to humanity, the moment the universe would begin to bend to our will. We were just simple creatures with sharp sticks and a want for more. As a result we formed small groups and although weak alone, we stood strong in numbers. We elected wise kings to lead our newly born nations and crafted flags adorned with the symbols of our ideologies and organizations. We forged sharp sticks that evolved into deadly blades to slay our enemies to gain fame and with each continent conquered it added to the melting pot which was our culture. Monuments stood long after our civilization’s vanish as a reminder of a golden era that crumbled to the dusts of time. Nations are born out of the ashes of these fallen nations heralding the rise of a more modern era.</summary></entry></feed>